{
"question": "葉書",
"answer": "はがき"
},
{
"question": "朝ご飯",
"answer": "あさごはん"
},
{
"question": "Ｙシャツ",
"answer": "ワイシャツ"
},
{
"question": "六つ",
"answer": "むっつ"
},
{
"question": "お手洗い",
"answer": "おてあらい"
},
{
"question": "お巡りさん",
"answer": "おまわりさん"
},
{
"question": "差す",
"answer": "さす"
},
{
"question": "零",
"answer": "れい"
},
{
"question": "二十日",
"answer": "はつか"
},
{
"question": "粁",
"answer": "キロメートル"
},
{
"question": "八つ",
"answer": "やっつ"
},
{
"question": "再来年",
"answer": "さらいねん"
},
{
"question": "燐寸",
"answer": "マッチ"
},
{
"question": "良く",
"answer": "よく"
},
{
"question": "其処",
"answer": "そこ"
},
{
"question": "小さな",
"answer": "ちいさな"
},
{
"question": "答える",
"answer": "こたえる"
},
{
"question": "もう一度",
"answer": "もういちど"
},
{
"question": "要る",
"answer": "いる"
},
{
"question": "背-1",
"answer": "せ"
},
